process.st 2019-05-03

# Privacy | Process Street | Checklist, Workflow and SOP Software

Last updated: June 8, 2018. Effective date: May 25th, 2018.   
You can see our previous Privacy Policy [here](https://www.process.st/privacy-archived/).

This Privacy Policy describes Goodwinds Inc.’s (here forth knows as Process Street) policies and procedures on the collection, use, and disclosure of your information when you use the Process Street Service. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy. Capitalized terms that are not defined in this Privacy Policy have the meaning given them in our [Terms of Service](https://process.st/terms). 

This policy covers:

  * Information We Collect
  * How We Use Your Information
  * How We Protect Your Information
  * Your Choices About Your Information
  * Process Street Blog & Community
  * International Data Transfer
  * Privacy Shield Notice
  * and other privacy information

By accessing or using the Service, you agree to this Privacy Policy. **If you do not agree with this policy, do not access or use the Service or interact with any other aspect of our business**.  Where we provide the Service under contract with an organization (for example your employer) that organization controls the information processed by the Service. For more information, please see Notice to End Users below.

## Information We Collect

Process Street uses the information we collect: 

  * to operate, maintain and provide you the features and functionality of the Service,
  * to analyze how the Service is used, diagnose service or technical problems,
  * to maintain security, personalize content, 
  * remember information to help you efficiently access your account, 
  * monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, traffic, and demographic patterns, 
  * and track Content and users as necessary to comply with the Digital Millennium Copyright Act and other applicable laws.

## Information You Provide

We collect information about you when you provide it to us, when you use our Service, and when other sources provide it to us, as further described below.  

**Account and Profile Information:** We collect information about you when you register for an account, create or modify your profile, set preferences, sign-up for or make purchases through the Service. For example, you provide your contact information and, in some cases, billing information when you register for the Service. You also have the option of adding a profile photo, job title, and other details to your profile information to be displayed in our Service.  We keep track of your preferences when you select settings within the Service. Your name, email address and other information you choose to provide on the Service will be viewable and discoverable by other users, in accordance with your settings on the Service.

If you choose to use our invitation service to invite a friend to the Service, we will ask you for that person’s email address and automatically send an email invitation. Process Street stores this information to send this email, to register your friend (team member) if your invitation is accepted, and to track the success of our invitation service.

**Content:** You also provide us information in Content you post to the Service. Your Content and metadata about your Content may be viewed by other users in accordance with your settings on the Service. Process Street can, but has no obligation, to monitor your Content you post on the Service. We can remove any information you post for any reason or no reason. Unless Content is made viewable in accordance with your settings on the Service, Process Street and Process Street employees will not view your Content except: (i) to maintain, provide or improve the Service; (ii) to help you and resolve your support requests; or (iii) as Process Street believes, in its sole opinion, is necessary to comply with or avoid the violation of applicable law or regulation or to cooperate with law enforcement.

## Information We Collect Automatically

**Cookies:** When you use the Service, we may send one or more “cookies” – a small data file – to your computer to uniquely identify your browser and let Process Street help you log in faster and enhance your navigation through the site. A cookie may convey anonymous information about how you browse the Service to us. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive after you close your browser so that it can be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Service. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser’s directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the Service may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled.

**Log Files:** When you use the Service, our servers automatically record certain information sent by your web browser. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, referring / exit pages and URLs, number of clicks and how you interact with links on the Service, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed, mobile carrier, and other such information.

**Clear Gifs Information:** When you use the Service, we may employ clear gifs (also known as web beacons) which are used to track the online usage patterns. In addition, we may also use clear gifs in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened by recipients. The information is used to enable more accurate reporting and make Process Street better for our users.

**Geo-Location Information:** When you use the Service by or through a mobile device, we may access, collect, monitor and/or remotely store “location data,” which may include GPS coordinates (e.g. latitude and/or longitude) or similar information regarding the location of your mobile device. Location data may convey information about how you browse the Service to us. Location data does not collect or share any personally identifiable information about you. Location data may be used in conjunction with personally identifiable information. Some features of the Service, particularly location-based services, may not function properly if use or availability of location data is impaired or disabled.

**Device Identifiers:** When you access the Service by or through a mobile device, we may access, collect, monitor and/or remotely store one or more “device identifiers.” Device identifiers are small data files or similar data structures stored on or associated with your mobile device, which uniquely identify your mobile device and are used to enhance the Service. A device identifier may be data stored in connection with the device hardware, data stored in connection with the device’s operating system or other software, or data sent to the device by us. A device identifier may convey information about how you use the Service to us. A device identifier does not collect or share any personally identifiable information about you. A device identifier may be used in conjunction with personally identifiable information. A device identifier may remain persistently on your device, to help you log in faster and enhance your navigation through the Service. Some features of the Service may not function properly if use or availability of device identifiers are impaired or disabled. Process Street may access, collect and/or store device identifiers upon enabling Process Street’s Service.

**Third Party Tools:** Process Street uses third-party analytics tools, such as Google Analytics, to help understand the use of the Service. Many of these tools collect the information sent by your browser as part of a web page request, including cookies and your IP address. These analytics tools also receive this information and their use of it is governed by their privacy policy.

## How We Use Your Information

We may use your email address to send you Service-related notices (including any notices required by law, in lieu of communication by postal mail). We may also use your contact information to send you marketing messages. If you don’t want to receive these messages, you can opt out by following the instructions in the message. If you correspond with us by email, we may retain the content of your email messages, your email address, and our responses.

**Your Use:** We will display your Personal Information in your profile page and elsewhere on the Service according to the preferences you set in your account. Any information you choose to provide should reflect how much you want others to know about you. Please consider carefully what information you disclose in your profile page and your desired level of anonymity. You can review and revise your profile information at any time. We may also share or disclose your information with your consent, for example, if you use a third party application to access your account (see below).

**Service Providers, Business Partners, and Others:** Process Street may share your personally identifiable information with other third parties for the purpose of providing the Service to you. If we do this, such third parties’ use of your information will be bound by this Privacy Policy. We may also store personal information in locations outside the direct control of Process Street (for instance, on servers or databases co-located with hosting providers).

**Business Transfers:** As we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets or business offerings. Customers, email, and visitor information is generally one of the transferred business assets in these types of transactions. We may also transfer or assign such information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers, or dissolution.

**Third Party Services:** We may share your information with a third party application with your consent, for example when you choose to access our Service through such an application. 

**Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement Requests; Protection of Process Street’s Rights:** Process Street may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that it is reasonably necessary to comply with a law, regulation or legal request; to protect the safety of any person; to address fraud, security or technical issues; or to protect Process Street’s rights or property.

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information:** We may disclose your non-private, aggregated, or otherwise non-personally identifiable information, such as anonymous usage data, platform types, etc., with interested third parties to help them understand the usage patterns for the Service.

## Legal bases for processing (for EEA users)

If you are an individual in the European Economic Area (EEA), we collect and process information about you only where we have legal bases for doing so under applicable EU laws.  This means we collect and use your information only where:

  * We need it to provide you the Service, including to operate the Service, provide customer support and personalized features and to protect the safety and security of the Service;
  * It satisfies a legitimate interest (which is not overridden by your data protection interests), such as for research and development, to market and promote the Service and to protect our legal rights and interests;
  * You give us consent to do so for a specific purpose; or
  * We need to process your data to comply with a legal obligation.

If you have consented to our use of information about you for a specific purpose, you have the right to change your mind at any time, but this will not affect any processing that has already taken place.  Where we are using your information because we or a third party (e.g. your employer) have a legitimate interest to do so, you have the right to object to that use though, in some cases, this may mean no longer using the Service. 

## How We Protect Your Information

The security of your information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) as part of our service, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

Process Street uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information, once we receive it. For example, we continuously and regularly back up your data to help prevent data loss and aid in data recovery. We also guard against common web attack vectors, host data in secure SAS 70 audited data centers, and implement firewalls and access restrictions on our servers to secure our network and better protect your information. No method of electronic transmission of storage is 100% secure, however, and we cannot ensure or warrant the absolute security of any information you transmit or store in the Service.

In the event that personal information is compromised as a result of a breach of security, Process Street will promptly notify those persons whose personal information has been compromised, in accordance with the notification procedures set forth in this Privacy Policy, or as otherwise required by applicable law.

## Your Choices About Your Information

You may, of course, decline to submit personally identifiable information through the Service, in which case Process Street may not be able to provide certain services to you. You may update or correct your account information at any time by logging in to your account. 

## Data Retention

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

## Process Street Blog & Community

Our Service offers publicly accessible community services including blogs, and forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. Your posts may remain even after you cancel your account.

## International Data Transfer

We collect information globally and primarily store that information in the United States. We transfer, process and store your information outside of your country of residence, to wherever we or our third-party service providers operate for the purpose of providing you the Service.  Whenever we transfer your information, we take steps to protect it. 

## Privacy Shield Notice

Process Street participates in and has certified its compliance with the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework. Process Street is committed to subjecting all personal data received from European Union (EU) member countries and Switzerland, respectively, in reliance on the Privacy Shield Frameworks, to the Framework’s applicable Principles. If there is any conflict between the terms of this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield Framework, visit the U.S. Department of Commerce’s Privacy Shield List: [https://www.privacyshield.gov/list.](https://www.privacyshield.gov/list)‍

Process Street is responsible for the processing of personal data it receives, under each Privacy Shield Framework, and subsequently transfers to a third party acting as an agent on its behalf. Process Street complies with the Privacy Shield Frameworks for all onward transfers of personal data from the EU and Switzerland, including the onward transfer liability provisions.‍

With respect to personal data received or transferred pursuant to the Privacy Shield Frameworks, Process Street is subject to the regulatory enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission. In certain situations, Process Street may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact JAMS, our U.S.-based third-party dispute resolution provider (free of charge), at [https://www.jamsadr.com/eu-us-privacy-shield](https://www.jamsadr.com/eu-us-privacy-shield).

Under certain conditions, more fully described on the Privacy Shield website: [https://www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=How-to-Submit-a-Complaint](https://www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=How-to-Submit-a-Complaint), you may be entitled to invoke binding arbitration when other dispute resolution procedures have been exhausted.

Process Street is liable under the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Principles for its agents to process transferred Personal Information in a manner consistent with the Principles.

## Notice to End Users

Our Service is intended for use by organizations. Where the Service is made available to you through an organization (e.g. your employer), that organization is the administrator of the Service and is responsible for the accounts over which it has control. If this is the case, please direct your data privacy questions to your administrator, as your use of the Service is subject to that organization’s policies. We are not responsible for the privacy or security practices of an administrator’s organization, which may be different than this policy. 

Administrators are able to:

  * require you to reset your account password;
  * restrict, suspend or terminate your access to the Service;
  * access information in and about your account;
  * access or retain information stored as part of your account;

In some cases, administrators can also:

  * restrict, suspend or terminate your account access;
  * change the email address associated with your account;
  * restrict your ability to edit, restrict, modify or delete information

Even if the Service is not currently administered to you by an organization, if you use an email address provided by an organization (such as your work email address) to access the Service, then the owner of the domain associated with your email address (e.g. your employer) may assert administrative control over your account and use of the Service at a later date.  You will be notified if this happens. 

If you do not want an administrator to be able to assert control over your account or use of the Service, use your personal email address to register for or access the Service.  If an administrator has not already asserted control over your account or access to the Service, you can update the email address associated with your account through your account settings in your profile.  Once an administrator asserts control over your account or use of the Service, you will no longer be able to change the email address associated with your account without administrator approval.

Please contact your organization or refer to your administrator’s organizational policies for more information.

## Children’s Privacy

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. Our Service is not directed to persons under 16. Process Street does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 16 or knowingly allow such persons to register with the Service. If we become aware that we have collected personal information from a child under age 16 without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 16, please contact us at [support@process.st.](mailto:support@process.st)

## Links to Other Websites

We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from the Service, nor the information or content contained therein. Please remember that when you use a link to go from the Service to another website, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other website, including those that have a link on our website, is subject to that website’s own rules and policies.

## Changes to Our Privacy Policy

We may change this privacy policy from time to time. We will post any privacy policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice by adding a notice on the Service login screen, or by sending you an email notification. We will also keep prior versions of this Privacy Policy in an archive for your review.  We encourage you to review our privacy policy whenever you use the Service to stay informed about our information practices and the ways you can help protect your privacy.

If you disagree with any changes to this privacy policy, you will need to stop using the Service and deactivate your account(s), as outlined above.

## Contact Us

If you have questions or concerns about how your information is handled, please contact us at [support@process.st.](mailto:support@process.st)
